bulklink.org 2014-12-29

# BulkLink.org - Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement for www.bulklink.org

This privacy statement was last updated on January 1, 2014. Northstone Ltd. (the "Company") created this privacy statement in order to disclose the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Company and the Web site at [www.bulklink.org](http://www.bulklink.org/ "www.northstone.de") (the "Web Site"). Upon reading this privacy statement, you will know:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you by the Company through the Web Site?
  2. The organization collecting the information.
  3. How the information is used.
  4. With whom the information may be shared.
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the Company's control.
  7. How you can access and correct any inaccuracies in the information collected about you.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the Web administrator by [info@northstone.us](mailto:info@northstone.us)

## Web Site Privacy Statement

The Company will not share your information with outside parties unless otherwise required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on this Web site or us. The Company is the sole owner of the information gathered on this site. In addition, we do not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 13, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

## What Information is Collected and How it is Used?

### Product or Information Inquiry Forms

We collect contact information such as name, mailing address, email address, phone number, and company information such as company name. This information is used to provide you with the information you have requested. Your information is not shared with third parties and is never used for purposes other than those for which it was collected.

### Contact Us

We use email links areas of the site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. Your personal information is not shared with third parties and is never used for purposes other than those for which it was collected.

### Logged Files and Cookies

The Web Site logs IP addresses and browser types for systems administration purposes. These logs may be analyzed to improve the value of the materials available on the Web Site and to collect information on an aggregate basis about visitors. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information. No cookies are currently used by this site. 

### Links

The Web Site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that these Web sites' privacy policies may differ from those of this Web Site. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any Web site you may visit.

## Choices Regarding the Use of Your Information

### Product or Inquiry Forms

If you need to update the information, you supplied to us, or no longer wish to receive information from us, please send email to that effect to [info@northstone.us](mailto:info@northstone.us).

### Security

Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is a top priority. We have taken careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. If we receive any from you on our web site, it is stored behind a firewall. Our employees are aware of our privacy and security policies. Your information is only accessible to those employees and contractors who need it in order to perform their jobs.

### Notification of Changes

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection through this Web site, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already collected through our site, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change.

### Privacy Policy Compliance

If you feel that we have not complied with the policies outlined in this privacy statement, please contact us and we will take action.
